<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NALgen</title>
    <link>/NALgen/</link>
    <description>Recent content on NALgen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/NALgen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NALgen Analysis Pt.1</title>
      <link>/NALgen/post/multivariate-analysis_simulated-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/NALgen/post/multivariate-analysis_simulated-data/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here, I present the prequel to the NALgen method: using multivariate analyses to infer population structure in the simulated data as well as to find covariance between genetic and environmental data. In upcoming posts about modeling neutral and adaptive genetic variation across continuous landscapes, information about population structure will be used in creating the response variable, while transformed environmental data (based on genetic-environmental covariance) will be used as predictors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Landscape Genetic Simulations</title>
      <link>/NALgen/post/landscape-genetic-simulations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/NALgen/post/landscape-genetic-simulations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To evaluate the NALgen method of modeling neutral and adaptive genetic variation across continuous landscapes, I first generated several landscapes, and then simulated genotypes based on the generated landscapes. In this post, I break down the simulation steps.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/NALgen/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/NALgen/about/</guid>
      <description>NALgen (Neutral and Adaptive Landscape Genetics) is a method for modeling the process of gene flow and predicting the resulting pattern of (neutral and adaptive) genetic variation across (continuous) landscapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorials</title>
      <link>/NALgen/tutorials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/NALgen/tutorials/</guid>
      <description>Tutorials for the NALgen method are posted here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vignettes</title>
      <link>/NALgen/vignettes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/NALgen/vignettes/</guid>
      <description>Vignettes for the NALgen method are posted here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>