<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Population Structure on NALgen</title>
    <link>/NALgen/tags/population-structure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Population Structure on NALgen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/NALgen/tags/population-structure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NALgen Analysis Pt.0</title>
      <link>/NALgen/post/nalgen-analysis_pt0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/NALgen/post/nalgen-analysis_pt0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Non-negative matrix factorization, as implemented in the &lt;em&gt;LEA&lt;/em&gt; package, is a case of unsupervised machine learning; &lt;em&gt;LEA&lt;/em&gt; uses least-squares estimates of ancestry coefficients.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Entropy and Clustering</title>
      <link>/NALgen/post/determining_bestk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/NALgen/post/determining_bestk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Using minimum cross-entropy (MinXEnt) to determine the number of genetic clusters (K) is not always straightforward.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NALgen Analysis Pt.1 - Recap</title>
      <link>/NALgen/post/nalgen-analysis_pt1_recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/NALgen/post/nalgen-analysis_pt1_recap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The output of multivariate analyses in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/chazhyseni/NALgen/tree/master/data&#34;&gt;NALgen Analysis Pt.1&lt;/a&gt; post was dense (935 lines of code, 121 figures). In this recap, I wanted to highlight some of the results. Furthermore, I wanted to mention that the population structure inference methods I compared were all machine learning (classification) algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NALgen Analysis Pt.1</title>
      <link>/NALgen/post/multivariate-analysis_simulated-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/NALgen/post/multivariate-analysis_simulated-data/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here, I present the prequel to the NALgen method: using multivariate analyses to infer population structure in the simulated data as well as to find covariance between genetic and environmental data. In upcoming posts about modeling neutral and adaptive genetic variation across continuous landscapes, information about population structure will be used in creating the response variable, while transformed environmental data (based on genetic-environmental covariance) will be used as predictors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>